(
"ai_sub_version": "2.5.0",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 2,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 12,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "gemini-cli:gemini-3-flash-preview",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.1-flash-lite-preview",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"web_search_tool": "duckduckgo",
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"gemini_cli": (
"timeout": 600,
"overwrite_system_prompt": false
)
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": true,
"fps": 1,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": "libx264"
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"run": 3,
"max": 9,
"delay": 30
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false
)
キミのびっくりした顔、ほんっとに可愛いねぇ～
your startled face is so cute~
これって、ずっと楽しみにしてたんじゃないのぉ～？
Wasn't this what you were waiting for?
だって、推しと直接お話しできるんだよぉ～？
To be able to talk to your oshi~
あれれ～？なんで戻るボタンなんか何回も押してるのぉ～？
Hmm, why the frantic button pressing dear?
もしがして……オリーがこうやってお話しするの、イヤだったのかな～？
Don't tell me you actually dislike this kind of interaction~
え～っ？なんでスマホの電源切っちゃうのぉ～？
Aww why'd you turn off the phone?
キミってさ……オリーと話すの、ほんとうにイヤだったんだぁ～？
You really don't want to talk to me huh~
これからもっと楽しくなるよぉ～！
The fun is just about to begin~
ダーリン～
Darling~
存在証明 愛だって 愛だって 吐いたって
My proof of existence—It’s love, it’s love, I spit out and yet
あーねころんごろんで いやん いやん
Ahh, I don’t want to lie down and roll over, no way, no way
プリティプリティ ダイエットDAY
Pretty pretty, a diet day.
曖昧一回楽に
Ambiguous once, easy.
曖昧ミー快楽に
Ambiguous me, pleasure.
病み悪化してんだって 愛だ恋だなんだってんだ
My sickness is getting worse, love or romance, whatever it is.
生命線は愛だって 愛だ嘆いたって
My lifeline is love, it’s love, I’ve lamented.
あーでもないこうでもないな 寂しい寂しいナンセンスDAY
Ah, this is not it, that is not it either. A lonely nonsense day.
いっそ密会ラブに 節操無い一解 LOVE ME
Let's make it a secret love, no integrity, solve it, love me
溺れ奴隷 踊れどれ 亡霊だ
Drown, slave, dance, dance, a ghost
なにもない なにもない 私なにもない
There's nothing, there's nothing, I have nothing
変われない 変われない 私変われない
Unchangeable, unchangeable, I am unchangeable
わからない わからない 分かる分からない
I don’t know, I don’t know, I know I don’t know
はい目元以外は隠して
Hey, keep everything hidden except for my eyes
ダダダダダダダリダリダリン ファニーダリン
Da da da da da darling, funny darling
はい冴えない愛情論で おねだりん
Endure the muddy affection, oh, darling
ダダダダダダダリン ノリダティエンダティ
Da da da da da darling, riding da dirty and dirty
会いたい衝動埋めてよ ダダダリン
Stop the urge to see me, da da darling
ダダダダダダダダ
Da da da da da da da
無 無 無 無
None, none, none, none
無い無い純情 感情が行ったり来たり
There's no purity, my emotions go back and forth
ダダダダダダダダ
Da da da da da da da
無 無 無 無
None, none, none, none
無い無い純情 感情でダダダリン
None, no order, my emotions go da da darling
ダダダダダダダリン 愛だ 愛だって
Da da da da da darling, it's love, it's love
まあねころんごろんでニャンニャン
Well, rolling around, meow meow
喰い意地地ダイエットDAY
Gluttony diet day
もう精一杯で積み
I'm already at my limit
暴論お節介で無理
Unreasonable meddling is impossible
病み垢してんだって 承認 承認 絶対だ
I've got a vent account, approval is absolute
接待だ 接待だ
Entertainment, entertainment
なにもない なにもない 私なにもない
There's nothing, there's nothing, I have nothing
恥じない 恥じない 私恥じない
Unashamed, unashamed, I am unashamed
わからない わからない 分かる分からない
I don’t know, I don’t know, I know I don’t know
はい自撮りは全部加工して
Yes, all selfies must be edited
ダダダダダダダリダリダリン FUNNY (笑)
Da da da da da darling, funny (lol)
はい絶えない愛情論で 冷めたり
Endure the endless affection, cooling down
ダダダダダダダリン 無理だ DIRTY
Da da da da da darling, it's impossible, dirty
会いたい衝動止めてよ ダダダリン
Stop the urge to see me, da da darling
踊れ 叫べ 踊れ
Dance, scream, dance
ルラッパパ
Lu la pa pa
踊れ 唄え 踊れ
Dance, sing, dance
ルラッパパ
Lu la pa pa
もうドッキンドッキ脳 しんどきんどき脳
My heart is pounding, it's painful
はい素顔は全部失くして
Yes, lose your real face entirely
ダダダダダダダリダリダリン FUNNY (笑)
Da da da da da darling, funny (lol)
どうしようもない感情論には 笑ったり
Laughing at the hopeless emotional theory
ダダダダダダダリン 脳裏 DIRTY
Da da da da da darling, dirty in my mind
会いたい衝動埋めてよ ダダダリン
Fill the urge to see me, da da darling
なななななななな
Na na na na na na na na
無い無い反応 返答を期待したり
No response, expecting a reply
なななななななな
Na na na na na na na na
無い無い妄想 感情でダダダリン
No delusions, with emotions da da darling
無い無い純情 感情でダダダリン
No purity, with emotions da da darling
ねだりん
Pleading
待ちわびている大通り
On the main street I've been waiting for...
目眩しそうな人混み
In a dizzying crowd...
くるり回った包帯
spinning in bandages.
立ち止まってる坊坊
A standing boy, boy,
しまい切れてない表情
with an expression that can't be hidden.
どこ見てるの坊坊
Where are you looking, boy boy?
知らなーい
I don't know,
今なに
what now?
目と目と目止まった合図
Eye to eye to eye, the signal stopped.
ロングのロリーズ
Long Lories,
あとでね
later, okay?
黒文字
Black letters...
隠してもムダね
it's useless to hide it.
けけけけーたいみしてよ今から
Ke-ke-ke-let me see your phone from now on!
ねえ今から
Hey, from now on...
ねえいいでしょ
Hey, it's okay, right?
けーたいみしてよ
Let me see your phone.
拒んでるの予想通り
Refusing, just as I expected.
だって賭けたこの試み
After all, I bet on this attempt...
くるり回った包帯
spinning in bandages.
立ち止まっていないで
Don't just stand there,
怒ったりしないでよ
and don't get angry.
I need チュチュチュ
I need chu chu chu...
いらない
I don't need it,
いらだち
this irritation.
使い古しの愛も
Even worn-out love,
言い訳たちも
and all those excuses.
画面じゃなく
Not the screen...
ここ見て
look here.
取り上げるからね
I'm taking it away!
けけけけーたいみしてよ今から
Ke-ke-ke-let me see your phone from now on!
ねえ今から
Hey, from now on...
ねえいいでしょ
Hey, it's okay, right?
けーたいかしてよ今から
Lend me your phone from now on!
けけけけーたいかしてよ今から
Ke-ke-ke-lend me your phone from now on!
ねえ今すぐ
Hey, right now,
渡しなさい
hand it over.
ねえいいでしょ
Hey, it's okay, right?
けーたいみしてよ
Let me see your phone.
Oh! Akhirnya kamu bangun juga!
Oh! You finally woke up!
Hai, selamat pagi~
Hi, good morning~
Nyenyak kah tidurmu?
Did you have a good sleep?
Oh, here?
This is my room!
What was that?
It looks a bit different?
Ehehe~ Because...
I, uh, prepared this room just for us...
because it's a special room!
Yeah, I wanted to make our memory as special as possible...
so I worked really hard and I prepared the perfect scenery just for us!
Ollie even transported you here while you were still asleep.
I just didn't want you to be tired, is all.
I just love you so much that...
I want these feelings to properly reach you.
Huh? What's wrong?
I'm not like my usual self?
Hehe~ You're so silly.
I have no idea what you're talking about.
Oh! Wait! Don't go!
Where are you going?
Wow, I can't believe you ran away like that.
But you were so cute when you were so shy!
指切りげんまん ホラでも吹いたら
Pinky swear, if you tell a lie,
針でもなんでも 飲ませていただきま
I'll make you swallow a needle or whatever...
Monday
It doesn't matter if it's Sunday
鏡よ鏡よ
Mirror, mirror...
この世で一番 変わることのない愛をくれるのは
The one who gives the most unchanging love...
だれ
...in all the world, who is it?
No need to ask cause it's my darling
わたしの最後はあなたがいい
I want my last to be you
あなたとこのまま おさらばするより
Rather than saying goodbye to you like this...
死ぬのがいいわ
...I'd rather die
I'd rather die
三度の飯よりあんたがいいのよ
I'd choose you over three meals a day
あんたとこのまま おさらばするよか
Rather than saying goodbye to you like this...
死ぬのがいいわ
...I'd rather die
I'd rather die
それでも時々 浮つく My Heart
Yet sometimes my heart wavers
死んでも治らな 直してみせます baby
If it won't be fixed until death, I'll fix it, baby
Yeah I ain't nothin' but ya baby
失って初めて 気がつくなんて
Realizing only after losing it...
そんなダサいこと もうしたくないのよ
...I don't want to do something so uncool anymore
Goodbye
Oh don't you ever say ByeBye
わたしの最後はあなたがいい
I want my last to be you
あなたとこのまま おさらばするより
Rather than saying goodbye to you like this...
死ぬのがいいわ
...I'd rather die
I'd rather die
三度の飯よりあんたがいいのよ
I'd choose you over three meals a day
あんたとこのまま おさらばするよか
Rather than saying goodbye to you like this...
死ぬのがいいわ
...I'd rather die
I'd rather die
わたしの最後はあなたがいい
I want my last to be you
あなたとこのまま おさらばするより
Rather than saying goodbye to you like this...
死ぬのがいいわ
...I'd rather die
I'd rather die
三度の飯よりあんたがいいのよ
I'd choose you over three meals a day
あんたとこのまま おさらばするよか
Rather than saying goodbye to you like this...
死ぬのがいいわ
...I'd rather die
I'd rather die
それでも時々 浮つく My Heart
Yet sometimes my heart wavers
そんなダサいのは もういらないのよ
I don't need that uncool stuff anymore
ByeBye
I'll always stick wit' ya my baby
my baby.
ねぇ アナタには見えない事ばかり
Hey, there are so many sides to you that you can't see
アタシは見えている事を知らないの？
Don't you know that I can see them?
背中につけられた誰かのキスの跡
Someone's kiss mark left on your back
一人じゃ買う訳の無いそれも
Even that, which you'd never buy alone
見て見ぬフリなだけ
I'm just pretending not to see it
笑っちまう程に キュートなカノジョ
A girlfriend so cute it's laughable
常時奔放 狂気 短気
Always uninhibited, madness, short-tempered
怒鳴ってたって目が合って一撃
Even if she's yelling, one eye contact is a blow
洗脳完了 お上手
Brainwashing complete, well done
愛していいのさ 強く愛していいのさ
You can love her, love her strongly
ねぇ 表面から全身まで
Hey, from the surface to your whole body
脳天から先端まで 知りたいの
From the top of your head to your toes, I want to know
それから 最近聞いた音楽から
And from the music you've listened to lately...
散財した総額まで 完全把握しないと
...to the total amount you've spent, I must know it all
気が済まないの
I won't be satisfied
とやかく言ったって実際の問題は
No matter what I say, the actual problem is...
その眼中アタシ何割くらい担ってるか
...what percentage of your eyes do I occupy?
隠してないで 確信を頂戴
Don't hide it, give me some certainty
黙って語らず
Quietly, without a word...
笑っちまう程に キュートなカノジョ
A girlfriend so cute it's laughable
容姿端麗 耽美 甘美
Beautiful appearance, aesthetic, sweet
身勝手だって シックな素振り
Even if she's selfish, a chic behavior
瞬時酩酊 女冥利
Instant intoxication, the joy of being a woman
愛しちまうのさ されど愛しちまうのさ
I end up loving you, and yet I end up loving you
過去を喰らう程に ポップなエナジー
A pop energy that devours the past
排気口から香るラーメン
Ramen smelling from the exhaust port
騙し奪われる恋でもいいの
I don't mind a love that's deceived and stolen
だってこの恋は
Because this love...
めっちゃくちゃ可愛いでしょ
...is super cute, right?
笑っちまう程に キュートなカノジョ
A girlfriend so cute it's laughable
常時奔放 狂気 短気
Always uninhibited, madness, short-tempered
怒鳴ってたって目が合って一撃
Even if she's yelling, one eye contact is a blow
洗脳完了 お上手
Brainwashing complete, well done
困っちまう程に キュートなカノジョ
A girlfriend so cute it's troublesome
容姿端麗 耽美 甘美
Beautiful appearance, aesthetic, sweet
身勝手だって シックな素振り
Even if she's selfish, a chic behavior
瞬時酩酊 女冥利
Instant intoxication, the joy of being a woman
愛していんのさ 強く愛していんのさ
I love you, I love you strongly
夜の始まりさ Bunny Girl
It's the beginning of the night, Bunny Girl
誘惑される鼓動に
By the heartbeats that tempt me
弾け飛ぶ葛藤に愛を乾杯
A toast to love in the bursting conflict
伝えられなくても
Even if I can't convey it
恋の始まりさ Bunny Girl
It's the beginning of love, Bunny Girl
誰かを穿って 澄んだ君の目を
Prying into someone, harboring those clear eyes
孕んで
Conceiving
Bunny Girl
Lyrics, Music: AKASAKI
さあ
Now
キザなステップを刻んで
Take some stylish steps
仕事帰りの疲れは
The fatigue after work
私とこのグラスに
Is with me and this glass
さあ
Now
自分好みに綯って
Wind it to your liking
世間に対する気持ち
Your feelings toward the world
私に注いでみない？
Won't you pour them into me?
ありきたりなラブソングでも
Even in a common love song
愛が込められてるの
Love is poured into it
それでも汚れるのね
Even so, it gets tainted
君を見れば分かるの
I can tell by looking at you
下を向く君の目を
Your eyes that look down
無理やり剥ごうとはしない
I won't try to pry them open by force
だからそんな顔せず手を差し伸べて
So don't make that face, just reach out your hand
ほら
See?
夜の始まりさ Bunny Girl
It's the beginning of the night, Bunny Girl
誘惑される鼓動に
By the heartbeats that tempt me
弾け飛ぶ葛藤に愛を乾杯
A toast to love in the bursting conflict
伝えられてるはず
It should be conveyed
恋の始まりさ Bunny Girl
It's the beginning of love, Bunny Girl
誰かを穿って
Prying into someone
澄んだ君の目を孕んで
Harboring those clear eyes
君の愛を知った気で
Feeling like I know your love
ハイになっていて
Getting high
感度去っていて
Sensitivity fading away
毎度泣いていてさ
Crying every time
それくらいがいいんでしょ
That's good enough, isn't it?
さあ キザなステップを刻んで
Now, take some stylish steps
君の顔色 今では
Your complexion, now
マシになってきてるから
Because it's getting better
君に委ねるわ Bunny Girl
I'll leave it to you, Bunny Girl
私をあげるわ Bunny Girl
I'll give you myself, Bunny Girl
誘惑される鼓動に
By the heartbeats that tempt me
弾け飛ぶ葛藤に愛を乾杯
A toast to love in the bursting conflict
伝えられてるはず
It should be conveyed
夜の始まりさ Bunny Girl
It's the beginning of the night, Bunny Girl
誰かを穿って
Prying into someone
澄んだ君の目を孕んで
Harboring those clear eyes
わっ！
Booh!
見つけた！ずっと探してたんだ！
There you are! I was looking everywhere for you!
かくれんぼしてるなんて教えてくれなかったじゃないか～
You didn't tell me that we were playing hide and seek...
やった～！ついにオリーのネオンステージに来てくれたんだね！
Well, I see you've made it to my neon stage, ya!
どうかな？キラキラしてて可愛いでしょ？
How you like it? It's really pretty, right?
全力で頑張って作ったんだよ～！
I put a lot of effort into it!
ネオンもいっぱいあるの！
It's a lot of neons and whatnot!
君が隠れてる間に、
And um, while you were hiding,
こっそりお着替えもしちゃったの！
I had the time to change my clothes.
オリー、めっちゃ可愛くなったでしょ～？
oh~ Don't I look super cute~?
へへ～ まだまだ君のために
Hehe~ Actually, I still have a lot
準備したものがたくさんあるんだ～
that I prepared for you!
だから、このかくれんぼは
So I hope that we can put a rest
もう終わりにしよ～？
to this hide and seek.
えっ？ダメなの？
Hah? No?
ねえ、君……。
Hey, you...
ここに来てから、
since you got here,
なんだかずっと様子がおかしいよ？
you've been acting kind of weird...
You've been acting really weird
ever since you got here,
and I just don't understand.
You've been trying to get my attention
by liking my posts and commenting on them.
Isn't this what you wanted?
You... you love me, right?
Don't you want to spend more time with me?
Why are you not accepting my feelings?
You're supposed to be happy,
but you're acting so strange.
Uh... whoa! Wait, wait!
きみのサ終が効いてんだみょん
Your end-of-service is hitting me hard, meow.
サッドガール・セックス
Sad Girl Sex
どんだけ泣いたか　わかんないや
I don't even know how much I've cried.
つら　独りっぱ
It's hard being all alone.
ぽっかり空いて　埋まらないや
There's a gaping hole that won't be filled.
ほしい　ラブぴったん
I want a perfect love match.
中途半端な出会いじゃ　刺さらないや
A half-baked encounter just won't cut it.
やっぱり　無理かも　ばたんきゅー
Maybe it's impossible after all... lights out.
げっそりハートが　治んないや
My worn-out heart won't heal.
出してよ　すぐ　処方箋
Write me a prescription right now.
サヨナラの刺が　なんで抜けないの
Why can't I pull out this thorn of goodbye?
君の代わりの人型が　全然見つからない
I can't find anyone to take your place.
サッドガール・セックス
Sad Girl Sex
ウブの出棺
A naive funeral procession.
知ってどんな思いだっけな
I wonder what kind of feelings those were.
誰かと寝ても　寂しさが発火
Even if I sleep with someone, loneliness ignites.
きみのサ終が　効いてんだみょん
Your end-of-service is hitting me hard, meow.
サッドガール・セックス
Sad Girl Sex
ウブの接吻
A naive kiss.
きっとまた会えるなんてさ
Saying things like 'we'll surely meet again'...
思い出のキミに　食い散らかされっこ
I'm being devoured by memories of you.
きみのサ終が　効いてんだみょん
Your end-of-service is hitting me hard, meow.
ねえ　マンガ返してよ
Hey, give me back my manga.
最新話であのキャラ死んじゃったよ
That character died in the latest chapter.
教えてくれたバンド
The band you told me about,
メンバーがクスリで捕まっちゃったよ
a member got arrested for drugs.
一緒にいたこと消えないや
The time we spent together won't fade away.
全部が二人だった
Everything was about the two of us.
きっと君は今誰かといるの
You're probably with someone else right now.
あたしだけが課金中
While I'm the only one still paying the price.
サッドガール・セックス
Sad Girl Sex
ウブの出棺
A naive funeral procession.
嫉妬辛くて延命ってな
Prolonging life through painful jealousy.
上書きがしたい　どうしてくれるの
I want to overwrite it, what will you do for me?
愛のガチャガチャ　天井はない
Love's gacha has no pity limit.
サッドガール・セックス
Sad Girl Sex
ウブの没収
A naive confiscation.
ちょっとエグすぎない　本当さ
Isn't it a bit too cruel? Seriously.
涙の跡に　狂気が走った
Madness ran along the trails of tears.
愛のガチャガチャ　天井はない
Love's gacha has no pity limit.
もしもが叶う　素敵世界ならば
If this were a wonderful world where 'what-ifs' came true,
君はさよなら取り下げを　検討加速しちゃう
you'd be fast-tracking the withdrawal of your goodbye.
サッドガール・セックス
Sad Girl Sex
ウブの出棺
A naive funeral procession.
なんでこんな終わってんだろう
Why is it ending like this?
誰かと寝たら　埋められるようなレベルの愛だ？
A love that can be filled by sleeping with someone?
そんなんじゃない！
It's nothing like that!
サッドガール・セックス
Sad Girl Sex
ラブでぺちゃんこ
Crushed by love.
今でも思ってんだわ
I'm still thinking about it.
期待通りの地獄　もう戻れないの
The hell I expected, I can't go back now.
きみのサ終が　効いてんだみょん
Your end-of-service is hitting me hard, meow.
探せ続行
Continue the search.
だめだめよ
No, no way.
揺らせ熱情
Shake up the passion.
あせあせた
Feeling flustered.
探せ続行
Continue the search.
だめだめよ
No, no way.
きみの絶頂
Your peak.
効いてんだみょん
It's hitting me hard, meow.
檻の中　あたしの愛猫
Inside the cage, my beloved cat.
お帰りなさい　君にニャオ
Welcome back, meow to you.
悪い子ね　汚れたお身体で
You're a naughty one, with such a dirty body.
行きはよいで　帰りは怖い
Easy to come, but scary to leave.
愛を知らない飽き猫さん
A bored cat who knows nothing of love.
間抜けな愛嬌とかそりゃ結構
Your silly charm is quite something.
睨めっこ　ほらバレバレで
A staring contest, look, you're totally exposed.
もう躁　なんでお仕置きだ自己嫌悪
So manic, why? Time for punishment and self-loathing.
君はあたしだけの愛猫だ
You are my one and only beloved cat.
だんだん好きになりなさい
Slowly, learn to love me.
ダン ダンスキになる
Step by step, I fall for you
スキになるね 愛して
I'm falling in love, so love me
愛して 愛して
Love me, love me
ダン ダンスキになる
Step by step, I fall for you
スキになるね 愛して
I'm falling in love, so love me
可愛いね 首輪つけてニャオ
So cute, put on a collar, meow
大切に 撫でてあげるニャオ
I'll pet you carefully, meow
檻の中の子猫ちゃん
Little kitten inside the cage
愛のダンスさあ 踊りましょう
Let's dance the dance of love
喉鳴らし 摺り寄って
Purring and snuggling up
ほらどうぞ？ 睨めっこ
Here you go? A staring contest
あら甘えん坊さんね
Oh, what a spoiled little one
そっぽ向いても そりゃ結構
Even if you look away, that's fine
君はあたしだけの愛猫なの
You're my one and only pet cat
ダン ダンスキになる
Step by step, I fall for you
スキになるね
I'm falling in love
愛して 愛して
Love me, love me
ダン ダンスキになる
Step by step, I fall for you
スキになるね
I'm falling in love
愛して
Love me
逃げられやしないのよ
You can't escape
一生 愛を強いて
Forcing love for a lifetime
最高死んでたって君は愛猫さん
Even if I'm dead, you're my pet cat
ねえ、どこにいるの？
Hey, where are you?
うぅ〜、出てきてよ！
Ugh, come on out!
かくれんぼはもう終わりだと思ってたのに…
I thought hide and seek was already over...
もぉ〜、どこに隠れているの？
Geez, where are you hiding?
早く出てきて！
Come out quickly!
こんなに探させるなんて、信じられないわよ…
I can't believe you're making me look for you this much...
あっ！
Ah!
あはは！見つけたよ！
Ahaha! Found you!
今夜はどこにも行かないでね〜！
Don't go anywhere else tonight, okay!
言葉低く 濁る君の そろ髪が
Your hair, matching your low, thick words,
僕の心を 躍らせたんです
set my heart aflutter.
靡くだけ 今はそれだけで
Just swaying, for now that's enough
この身 屈めますから
for me to bend my body to you.
Midnight 光線 Darling
Midnight beam, Darling
堪えきれぬ 欲望に任せて
Surrender to the uncontrollable desire.
Midnight 光線 Darling
Midnight beam, Darling
僕に仕える 気になったら
If you feel like serving me...
願うは 三度の絶頂を
I wish for a triple climax
胸の中で 至る
reaching it within my chest.
今宵も僕らは 繁栄の
Tonight again, for the sake of prosperity,
ために 矢を 放つ
we fire an arrow.
抗いの 呟きとは 裏腹に
Contrary to my murmurs of resistance,
身体は 嬉しそうに 疼いたんです
my body throbbed with joy.
この首に 鎖を 付けるかは
Whether to put a chain on this neck
僕ら 次第ですから
is up to us.
真面目ですかね 淫らですかね
Are we serious, or are we lewd?
Midnight 光線 Darling
Midnight beam, Darling
愛と欲に 純白を 求めて
Seeking pure white in love and lust.
Midnight 光線 Darling
Midnight beam, Darling
僕を拒む 気になっても
Even if you feel like rejecting me...
願うは 三度の絶頂を
I wish for a triple climax
胸の中で 至る
reaching it within my chest.
零れる 涙が 飽和して
Spilling tears become saturated,
僕は 今に 果てる
and I am about to perish.
その溢れた 吐息の 原因なんだって
Whatever the cause of those overflowing sighs,
いったいどこから いったって ドキドキなんだって
no matter where it comes from, my heart pounds.
よろめく 恐怖が 原因なんだって
Even if staggering fear is the cause,
それでも 君なら いいんだって さらに
if it's you, it's fine, even more so.
願うは 三度の絶頂を
I wish for a triple climax
胸の中で 至る
reaching it within my chest.
今宵も僕らは 繁栄の...
Tonight again, we are...
あぁ　あぁ　あぁ　あぁ
Ah, ah, ah, ah
願うは三度の絶頂を
Wishing for a triple climax
胸の中で至る
Reaching inside my heart
零れる涙が飽和して
The overflowing tears saturate
僕は今に果てる
And I'm now coming to an end
ねえあたし知ってるよ　きみがひとり
Hey, I know, I know you're alone
してるの知ってるよ　ビクンビクン震えてさ
I know you're doing it, trembling and shaking
声もダダ漏れなんだわ
Your voice is leaking out, too
正直に言っちゃえよ
Just tell me honestly
バレてるんだし言っちゃえよ
You're busted, so just say it
効いてんの？
Is it working?
普通普通　恥ずかしい
It's normal, normal, you're just hiding your embarrassment
みんな隠しているだけ
Everyone is just hiding it
ねえあたし知ってるよ　きみがひとり
Hey, I know, I know you're alone
涙隠してるの知ってるよ
I know you're hiding your tears
グズグズへこんでさ
Moping and feeling down
弱いヒトからイン・ザ・ナイト
Starting from the weak ones, into the night
朝が来るまで一緒コース
We're on this together until morning
もっと泣いたって
Even if you cry more,
何度だって受け止めてあげる
I'll accept it all, no matter how many times
もう我慢しないで
Don't hold back anymore,
いっぱい出しちゃってね
just let it all out, okay?
うわお願いきみがほしいの
Oh, please, I want you
慰めさせて　シェイクシェイク
Let me comfort you, shake shake
アイの才能で
With the talent of love
泣いてくれなきゃ　枯れてしまう
If you don't cry, I'll wither away
濡れていたいたい　ねえいいでしょ？
I want to be wet, isn't that nice?
舐めとって　飲み干したいんだってば
I want to lick it up and drink it all
うわお願いきみがほしいの
Oh, please, I want you
頼り散らして　シックラブ
Depend on me completely, sick love
なんぞ最高ね
It's the best, isn't it?
わけてくれなきゃ　きみの痛い
If you don't share it with me, your pain
感じてたいの　ねえいいでしょ？
I want to feel it, isn't that nice?
吸いとって　救いたいんだってば
I want to suck it out and save you
ねえあたし知ってるよ
Hey, I know,
きみがひとり悔しがってんの知ってるよ
I know you're feeling frustrated all alone
ズキュンズキュン高まるよ
My heart's racing more and more
きみを襲うことはやめない
I won't stop attacking you
ねえあたし知ってるよ
Hey, I know,
きみはできる子知ってるよ
I know you're a capable person
しんどいときは　弱い位でちょうどいい
When it's tough, being weak is just right
あたしそれでも好きだよ
I still love you anyway
うわお願いきみがほしいの
Oh, please, I want you
名前を呼ぶのよ　いざ参上
Call my name, I'm here now
会いに参上
I've come to see you
きみはひとりだ　だから歌う
You're alone, so I'll sing
ひとりじゃないの　ねえいいでしょ？
You're not alone, isn't that nice?
ソロプレイはおしまいなんだってば
Solo play is over now, I tell you
きみがやめるときも　あたしそばにいるわ
Even when you quit, I'll be by your side
いつも見守っているわ
I'll always be watching over you
そう　怖くないのよ
That's right, there's nothing to fear
あぁ
Ah
うわお願いきみがほしいの
Oh, please, I want you
慰めさせて　シェイクシェイク
Let me comfort you, shake shake
アイの才能で
With the talent of love
泣いてくれなきゃ　枯れてしまう
If you don't cry, I'll wither away
濡れていたいたい　ねえいいでしょ？
I want to be wet, isn't that nice?
舐めとって　飲み干したいんだってば
I want to lick it up and drink it all
うわお願いきみがほしいの
Oh, please, I want you
頼り散らして　シックラブ
Depend on me completely, sick love
なんぞ最高ね
It's the best, isn't it?
わけてくれなきゃ　きみの痛い
If you don't share it with me, your pain
感じてたいの　ねえいいでしょ？
I want to feel it, isn't that nice?
吸いとって　救いたいんだってば
I want to suck it out and save you
ふぅ！　ぷはー！
Fluuh! Phew!
やっと終わったよ！　わあ！
Finally done! Wow!
これで、もう逃げ出したりしないからな〜
This way, you won't be running away anymore!
いい子にしてじっとしててね〜？
Now be good and sit tight, okay?
本当に汗ばむほど働いちゃったわ！
You really made me work up a sweat!
あなたを探して追いかけ回しちゃった〜
I had to look for you and chase you down...
やっとまた一緒にいられて嬉しいよ〜
But I'm just glad that we're finally together again.
ついに二人きりで一緒に過ごせるんだ〜！！
Now that we're finally alone, we get to spend some time together!
おい
Hey.
こっちを見ろよ...
Look at me.
いい子いい子〜
Good boy, good boy.
さて、皆さんの注意を引けたところで
Alright, now that I have your attention...
ついに私がずっと取り組んできたものをお見せできます！
I can finally show you what I've been working on all this time!
これを見てください！
Check this out!
今回も、誕生日グッズが出ます！
Birthday goods are coming out this year too!
Kali ini juga akan ada merchandise yang datang!
There will also be merchandise coming this time!
There will also be birthday goods for this year, so I'll be introducing it to you guys one by one, okay?
はい！じゃあ、最初のアイテムはこちら！
Alright! Now, here is the first item!
うわあ！とってもワイドなラバーマット！
Whoa! A very wide rubber mat!
可愛くないですかこれ？もう四六時中...
Isn't this cute? All day and all night...
Always think of Ollie Wide Rubber Mat.
Wherever you're working, wherever you're gaming, you always remember me.
This... it kind of looks like a yandere, doesn't it?
But I'm not a yandere, I'm just your girlfriend. Hehe.
「オリ一のこと、いつも考えて♡」ワイドラバ一マット
Always think of Ollie Wide Rubber Mat.
普段使いにおすすめのちょっと大きめサイズです！
It's a slightly large size, recommended for everyday use!
そしてイラストは、花澤明先生です！
And the illustration is by Hanasawa Akera-sensei!
花澤明先生！ありがとうございます！
Hanasawa Akera-sensei! Thank you very much!
Okay, then the next item will be... こちら！
Okay, then the next item will be... this one!
Wow, it's a pillow! Isn't this so cute?
クッションだよ！Banget!
It's a cushion! So much!
「オリ一のこと、いつも夢に見て♡」
Always dream of Ollie.
寝るときも私のことを思い出して、私の夢を見てね。
When you sleep, remember me and dream of me.
これ、すごくふわふわそうなので、安眠のためにぜひゲットしてください！
This looks so fluffy, so please get it for a good night's sleep!
Alright, and followed by... こちら！
Alright, and followed by... this one!
It's a ring necklace! Well, it's a ring,
if it doesn't fit your size then you can just wear it as a necklace, isn't that really cool?
さて、これはね、指輪。
So this is a ring.
でも、もしサイズが合っていないなら、ネックレスとしても使うことができます！
But if the size doesn't fit, you can also use it as a necklace!
Ah! It's so cute! So make sure that when you go out, you wear this,
so that whenever you go grocery shopping,
no other girls out there will be hitting on you.
はい、そして次はこちら！
Yes, and then we also have... this one!
It's a mug! Isn't it so cute?
I really like the design!
So not only when you're working, or gaming, or grocery shopping,
or... uh... sleeping,
but even when you're drinking, you think of me!
そしてもちろん、これも忘れないで... こちら！
And of course, not forgetting... this one!
3ヶ国語のシチュエーションボイス！
Situational voices in three languages!
日本語、インドネシア語、そして英語！
In Japanese, Indonesian, and English!
うわー、いつものように、さすが私！さすが私！
Wow, as always, sasuga me! Sasuga me!
はい、そして最後に、フルセットを購入いただいた方には、
Yes, and finally, for those who purchased the full set,
数量限定で、直筆サイン入りチェキ風ブロマイドカードがついてきます。
a limited quantity of handwritten signed instax-style bromide cards will be included.
And for those of you guys who buy the full set, there will be a limited edition postcard
with my message and my sign! Yeah!
Jadi buat kalian yang beli full set-nya itu, bakal dapet postcard dari Ollie,
So for those of you who buy the full set, you'll get a postcard from Ollie,
ada message, ada tanda tangannya juga. です！
with a message and a signature too. Desu!
次は、通常版は、箔押し複製サイン入り
Next, the regular version comes with a foil-stamped replica signature
チェキ風ブロマイドカードがついてきます。
instax-style bromide card.
And for those of you who buy like the normal version,
you guys can also get the postcard with my sign and message!
Yang beli versi biasa juga akan dapat postcard yang ada message dan sign-nya.
Those who buy the normal version will also get a postcard with a message and signature.
Yap, itu aja... Jadinya panjang, ya? ちょっと長くなっちゃったかな？
Yep, that's all... It got quite long, didn't it?
でも私のグッズ、買ってくれるよね？
But you'll buy my merch, won't you?
TOPBGT!! やったー！
TOPBGT!! Yay!
Sebenarnya aku masih mau main sama kamu sih. もっと君と一緒に遊べたらいいんだけど、
Actually, I still want to play with you. I wish I could spend more time with you,
tapi udah waktunya kita berpisah... 残念ながら時間は限られているんだ... Damn!
but it's already time for us to part... Unfortunately, our time is limited... Damn!
Tapi sebelum itu, Ollie masih ada hadiah buat kamu! でもその前に一つだけ、あなたに贈りたいものがあるの！
But before that, Ollie has one last gift for you! There's one thing I want to give to you!
Jadi tolong dengarkan ya〜 だからちゃんと聞いてね〜 Don't go anywhere! Hehehehe.
So please listen, okay? So listen closely, okay? Don't go anywhere! Hehehehe.
こっちを向いて
Look this way
声を聞かせて
Let me hear your voice
私を見て
Look at me
私一番ね
I'm number one, right?
ゾッとした顔が可愛いね
I love that face you make when terrified
君のその身体が欲しいの
That body of yours, want it so badly to be mine, oh
Loveit? Loveit?
Love it? Love it?
Lali. Loveit. High.
Lali. I love it. High.
可哀想ね君は悪い子なのね
Poor thing, you're such a bad boy.
どの顔がお好きで 散々
Which face do you like? Scattered.
色目が お上手で 頭沸き
You are still very good at using colorful eyes. My head hurts.
君に踊らされちゃって アタシは狂う
You make me dance. I'm going crazy.
What is Loveit?
君の血肉まで
Down to your flesh and blood
骨の髄まで
Even to the marrow of your bones
入れてから空っぽになる 愛のパペット
Filling me up until I'm empty, a puppet of love
胸が苦しいね
My chest hurts, doesn't it?
息が詰まるのね
My breath catches, doesn't it?
それが恋と教えてあげる あはは
That's what love is, I'll teach you. Ahaha.
虚ろな声で ほら囁いて
With a vacant voice, look, whisper
いい子ね 首輪付けた君は Loveit
Good boy, you with the collar on, Loveit
イカれちゃった？
Have you gone crazy?
Noね 恋は盲目ね
No, love is blind, isn't it?
したいよね してあげるわ
You want to, don't you? I'll do it for you.
逝って？ あはは
Go? Ahaha.
濡れて君の紅い跡 溺れるまで
Drenched in your red marks until I drown
痛い痛いの飛んで行け 痺れるまで
Pain, pain, go away, until I'm numb
愚かね
How foolish.
間抜けな顔して
With that stupid look on your face,
君は悪い子なの
you're such a bad child.
痛いのが好きで
You love the pain,
産に修に
amidst the suffering.
あら お口はチャックで
Oh, keep your mouth zipped.
何？何？
What? What?
性に踊らされちゃう
You're driven by your instincts.
君を喰らう
I'll devour you.
血肉の中まで
Into your flesh and blood,
骨の髄まで
into the marrow of your bones,
しゃぶりつくせば
if I suck them all dry,
もう空っぽの
then your empty...
胸が苦しいね
chest will hurt, won't it?
息が詰まるのね
You're suffocating, aren't you?
それが恋と
That this is love...
教えてあげる
is what I'll teach you.
君はピエロね
You're just a clown,
愛を囁いて
whispering words of love.
人間の形した君はラベル
You, in human form, are just a label.
イカれちゃったのね
You've gone mad, haven't you?
恋は盲目ね
Love is blind, you see.
したいよね
You want to do it,
してあげるわ
so I'll do it for you.
いって
Go on.
報い 贖い
Retribution, atonement...
穢れたちに溺れるまで
until you drown in filth.
痛い 痛いの飛んで行け
Pain, pain, go away...
息が止まるまで
until your breath stops.
報い 贖い
Retribution, atonement...
穢れたちに溺れるまで
until you drown in filth.
痛い 痛いの飛んで行け
Pain, pain, go away...
息が止まるまで
until your breath stops.
CAST
hololive Indonesia
Kureiji Ollie (holoro)
Vestia Zeta (holoh3ro)
hololive 4th generation
Amane Kanata
hololive English
Takanashi Kiara (Myth)
HOLOSTARS
Minase Rio (UPROAR!!)
Special guest
Michi Mochievee
CREDIT
Thumbnail / 3D Animation
k3nzoteruya
Tuning, Mix, Mastering
Kururu
Lyric Overlay
Maad
SNS Promotion Assets
Altersky
Choreography
FreeM
Special thanks
トライフロンティア合同会社
すくろーす
Tri-Frontier LLC
Sucrose
クックルP / as
KukkuruP / as
合同会社VESSEL LIFE
um.
VESSEL LIFE LLC
Koudai / Toshiyuki
Crazy になるほど 恋している ZOMBIE
Crazy to the Point of Loving You ZOMBIE
3Dライブを見てくれてありがとう！
Thank you so much for coming to watch the 3D Live!
オーリーの愛、ちゃんと届いたかな？
How was it? Did you feel my love?
そう！特別に用意したお部屋、可愛かったでしょ？
Oh, look at that! A specially prepared bedroom!
ベッドやソファ、それにウディンもいたし...
It has a bed, a sofa, Udin, and...
オーリーが大事にしてる人たちの写真も
And I don't know if you noticed, but there was...
飾ってあったんだよー！
...a display photo of my most cherished people.
ネオンステージもかっこよかったでしょ！
I think the neon stage was really cool too!
テレビがいっぱい並んでたの、見た？
You probably spotted a bunch of TVs around.
あれね、オーリーが君のことを遠くから見られるように置いてあったんだよ～
They're there so I can watch you from afar.
すごいでしょ？
Cool, right?
あ...でも、何回も連れ回しちゃったね
Uh, but I really did drag you around, huh?
大丈夫？疲れてない？
Um, how are you? Do you feel sick? Are you okay?
あ...まあ、寝てる間に運んだから、問題ないかなって思ってるけど...
I carried you while you slept, so it's fine...
あ！そういえば！
Huh? What? No, nothing! I didn't say anything!
なんか途中で怖がって逃げたり、避けたりしてたでしょ～？
Speaking of you, you kept hiding from me!
ふふ、悪い子なんだから～！
Naughty, naughty! Tsk, tsk!
いつもコメントしたり、いいねしてくれたり、
You always leave comments and like my posts,
会いに来てくれてたんだけど
so I thought you'd like it if I visited!
そんなに驚かせちゃうとは思わなかったよ
I didn't think it would surprise you that much.
急に目の前に現れたから、びっくりしすぎちゃったのかな？？
Maybe you were too surprised when I appeared?
うん、ふーん...
Yeah, hmm...
オーリーはね、君のためにたくさん頑張ったんだよ～
But just so you know, I worked hard for you!
衣装を何度も着替えたり、歌の練習もたくさんしたの！
I sang a lot and changed outfits many times!
オーリーの愛、ちゃんと届いたかな？
And I wonder if my feelings reached you?
...届いたよね？？
It obviously did, right?
最後は、やっと君を捕まえちゃった！
Also, at the end, I finally managed to catch you!
それって君も望んでたんでしょ？？
That's what you hoped for, right?
だってずっと逃げてたんだもん！
I mean, 'cause you were running away from me
オーリーのことが大好きだから、そうなっちゃうって分かってたんだよ？ね？
because you love me! You expected it too, right?
うんうん！やっぱりそうだよね！
Hehe, period!
じゃあ、まだ見てくれてるみんなに
Anyway, for those of you who are still watching,
お知らせだよー！
thank you by the way. I have an announcement!
SO87の新曲「Love Me Back」に出演して、
I'll be featured in SO87's song 'Love Me Back'
なんとMVにも出ちゃいます！
with the music video!
すごーくかっこいいから、みんなちゃんとチェックしてね～！
It's going to be cool, so keep an eye out!
ワクワクするでしょ～？
Ah, it's just so exciting, isn't it?
もしまたオーリーの「愛」を感じたくなったら
If you ever feel the need to feel my love again,
いつでも3D生配信を見に来てね！
come back to watch the 3D Birthday Live!
オーリーはずーっとここで待ってるんだからね～！
Ollie will always be here, waiting for you!
バイバイ！
Bye-bye!
オックレイジー！
Otsucrazy!